Guide to the George Nicolau Papers WAG.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- OCA / Suffolk County Court Employees Association (94/96), 363221 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- OCA / DC 37, AFSCME and Local 1070 (ER 94/40; Court Interpreters), 363220 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Suffolk / SDA (1587 98; Payment of Travel Pay), 363219 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Suffolk Water / UWUA Local 393 ( 8-81), 363218 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Suffolk County PBA & County of Suffolk, 363217 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Suffolk County PBA & County of Suffolk (3 Grievances), 363216 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- SUNY / UUP (80-08-1001), 363215 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- TBTA / BTOBA (1739 93), 363214 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- TBTA / SOBA (1792 97), 363213 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Transportation Authority / TSBA (Surviving Spouse Benefits; Grievance LR-6004), 363212 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- TBTA / TBTA Superior Officers Benevolent Assoc. (01348 91; overtime on RDO), 363211 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- TBTA / TBA 1511 92; Claim of James Denig, 363210 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- TBTA / DC 37 (1851 91; Overtime), 363209 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Time Warner / Guild (197 96), 363208 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Time Warner / Guild (Time Digital and Guild Jurisdiction), 363207 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Time Warner / Local 3 IBEW (470 99; Discharge of Francis Ventura), 363206 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- TWU Local 100 Schermerhorn / James, 363205 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Trane / Local 730, United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry of the United States and Canada (81K/06953), 363204 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Trojan Steel Corp. / Shopmens Local Union #455 (Borhi & Rivera), 363203 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- UFT / Lutheran Medical Center (753 00), 363202 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- UPS / Local 177, IBT (453 96L; DallaPorta), 363201 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- UPS / Local 177, IBT (81 95L; Seniority and Sixth Day Call), 363200 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- UPS / IBT National (1908 98), 363199 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- UPS / Teamsters Local 30 (2940 02; Hohider), 363198 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- UPS / IBT National (1548 99), 363197 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- UPS / Local 177, IBT (721 96; Fulltime Shuttle Drivers Supervisors Working), 363196 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- UPS / IBT (543 96), 363195 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Local 259, UAW / Bronx Westchester Mack Corp., 363194 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Local 259 UAW / Silver Chrysler (J. Giordano), 363193 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Whitney Blake Co. / United Electrical, Radio, & Machine Workers of America, 363192 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- IATSE / WOR Division of RKO-General, 363191 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- AFGE Local C-111 / U.S. Customs (FMCS 76K 19403), 363190 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- West Orange NJ Teachers (72 92D), 363189 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Western Publishing / Local 274, Graphic Communications International Union, 363188 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- WPIX / Local 1212, IBEW (9295-6; Holiday Pay), 363187 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- US Food Service / IBTL Local 559, 363186 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- USWA Local 285 / Armstrong World Industries (610 01), 363185 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Yonkers Bd. Of Ed. / Yonkers Fed. of Teachers (general), 363184 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Yonkers Federation of Teachers and Yonkers Bd. of Ed. (re: assignment of double classes), 363183 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Yonkers Fed of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed. (S. Kotler), 363182 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Yonkers Fed. Of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed. (Linton & Chapman), 363181 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Yonkers Fed. of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed (More Effective Schools Program), 363180 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Yonkers Fed of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed (C. Reale), 363179 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Yonkers Fed. of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed (Sabbatical Leaves), 363178 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Yonkers Fed. of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed. (Sabbatical Leaves 1976 77), 363177 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Younkers Fed. of Teachers / Younkers Board of Ed (use of school aide as teacher), 363176 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Zionist Organization of America / D. C. 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees Union, AFSCME (1249-88), 363175 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- NABET, Local 31 / NBC (1630-0022-75), 363174 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- NABET, AFL-CIO, CLC / NBC (Grievance #NW-74-1), 363173 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- NABET, Local 31 / NBC (Grievance Number NW 74-14), 363172 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- NABET / NBC (Recording by W. Hall for Update), 363171 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- NABET, AFL-CIO, CLC / NBC (Transfer of Work NW 74-16), 363170 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- NBC / NABET (Grievance Number NW 75-14), 363169 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- NBC / NABET (Gr. No. NW 75-33), 363168 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- NABET NBC (NW 75-56), 363167 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- NABET / NBC (NW 76-27) Videotape Eds, - Meal Periods), 363166 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- NABET / NBC (NW 76-32; Permanent Upgrading-Radio), 363165 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- NABET / NBC (NW 76-34; Anniversary Raise C. Conway), 363164 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- NABET / NBC (NW 76-39; Payback Day Requests), 363163 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- NABET / NBC (NW 76-41; Violations of NW 75-12), 363162 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- NABET / NBC (NW 76-48; Chiron Upgrading), 363161 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- NBC / NABET (NW 76-60; R. McKay Improper Seniority), 363160 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- NBC / NABET (NW 77-12; Chenevert II), 363159 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- NABET / NBC (NW 78-47), 363158 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- NABET / NBC (NW 78-47R), 363157 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- NABET / NBC (NW 78-52), 363156 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- NABET / NBC (NW 79-8; NW 78-5), 363155 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- NBC / NABET (NW 79-14), 363154 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- NABET / NBC (NW 79-38), 363153 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- NABET / NBC (NW 79-17), 363152 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- NABET / NBC (NW 80-8), 363151 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- NABET / NBC (NW 80-7), 363150 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- NABET /NBC (NW 80-12), 363149 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- NABET / NBC (NW 80-16 (Taylor), 363148 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- NABET / NBC (NW 80-24), 363147 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- NABET / NBC (NW 80-26), 363146 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- NABET / NBC (NW 80-35), 363145 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NABET / NBC (NW 81-1), 363144 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- NABET / NBC (NW 81-2), 363143 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- NABET / NBC (NW 81-4), 363142 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- NABET / NBC (NW 81-6; Schindler), 363141 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- NABET / NBC (NW 81-21 & 22; Ross and Batton), 363140 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- NABET / NBC (NW81-26), 363139 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- NABET / NBC (NW 81-27), 363138 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- NABET / NBC (NW 81-61), 363137 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- NABET / NBC (NW 82-16), 363136 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- NABET / NBC (NW 82-28), 363135 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- NABET / NBC (NW 82-34; Lopez), 363134 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- NABET / NBC (NW 85-17), 363133 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- NABET / NBC (NW 85-21), 363132 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- NABET / NBC (NW 85-76 & 77), 363131 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- NABET / NBC (NW 86-106), 363130 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- NABET / NBC (NWM 77-1), 363129 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- NABET / NBC (NWA 78-1), 363128 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- NABET / NBC (NWM 80-1 and NWA 80-3), 363127 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- NABET / NBC (NWM 80-2), 363126 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- NABET / NBC (NWA 80-1), 363125 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- NABET / NBC (NWM 81-2), 363124 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- ABC / DGA (35-80; Washington Radio Practice), 363123 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- ABC / DGA (6:564; KTNV, WXYZ), 363122 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- ABC / DGA (Selchert), 363121 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- ABC / DGA (Steinmetz), 363120 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- CBS / DGA (D. Bona), 363119 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- CBS / DGA (6 CBS 534; Sports Directors and Associate Directors), 363118 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- NBC / DGA (Eric Bell), 363117 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- NBC / DGA (Disco suspension), 363116 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- NBC / DGA (Disciplinary Memo), 363115 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- NBC / DGA (Gulf War Parade; 91 NBC 873), 363114 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- NBC / DGA (First Class Travel), 363113 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- NBC/ DGA (Promos), 363112 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- NBC / DGA (Sunday Today), 363111 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- NBC / DGA (minicams), 363110 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- NBC / DGA (7:647 Night News Graphics), 363109 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- NBC / DGA (Gary Weis), 363108 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- NBC / DGA (minicam 7 NBC 723), 363107 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- DGA / Illustra Films, 363106 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- DGA / Rothberg, 363105 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- ABC / WGA (Barry), 363104 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- WGA / ABC (1419 92; Lubart), 363103 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- WGA / ABC (1231 81 newswriters), 363102 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- WGA / York Enterprises (David Axlerod), 363101 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- WGA / CBS (0962; 81Busch and Hicks), 363100 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- WGA, East / CBS (Editors fees), 363099 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- WGA / CSB (1583 82; Newswriter Workload), 363098 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- WGA, East / CBS (Lane Vernardos Case), 363097 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- WGA / CBS (Discharge of Roger Feinman), 363096 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- WGA / Gaberock Enterprises (Price and Antonacchi), 363095 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- WGA / Manhattan Entertainment (Malko), 363094 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- WGA / Tilos Productions, 363093 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- L. 144, Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Health Services Union / Brookhaven (Simmons Discharge), 363092 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- SNY / L. 144 (Brookhaven; Ellis), 363091 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- L. 144 / Cobble Hill (Barthelemy), 363090 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Fieldston / L. 144 (Lateness Policy), 363089 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Franklin / L. 144 (Eve St. Juste), 363088 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Franklin / L. 144 (Vado), 363087 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- SNY / L. 144 (Williamsbridge / Wiggan), 363086 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- SNY / L. 144 (Shoreview; Grospe), 363085 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle Home for the Aged (Gonzalez), 363084 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Clearview / L. 144 (S. Young), 363083 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Altshuler), 363082 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Altshuler termination), 363081 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- L. 144 / Beth Israel (355 97; Carter), 363080 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Beckford), 363079 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Roberta Best), 363078 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Jack Crocitto), 363077 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (10 % Differential), 363076 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- L. 144, SEIU / Brooklyn Hospital (Free Parking Rights), 363075 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Francis Ellington), 363074 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (L. Friedman), 363073 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Friedman Suspension), 363072 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Discharge of F. Gonzales), 363071 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Guy), 363070 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Lindsey), 363069 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Goldie Hoffman), 363068 (Box 5, Folder 85)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Holiday Pay / Call-In Pay), 363067 (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Hollar), 363066 (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Jones), 363065 (Box 5, Folder 88)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Johnstone), 363064 (Box 5, Folder 89)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Malcolm), 363063 (Box 5, Folder 90)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Newman), 363062 (Box 5, Folder 91)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Newman), 363061 (Box 5, Folder 92)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (H. Ortiz), 363060 (Box 5, Folder 93)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Richards), 363059 (Box 5, Folder 94)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (RN In-charge Pay), 363058 (Box 5, Folder 95)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Antonio Rodriguez), 363057 (Box 5, Folder 96)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Roman Suspension), 363056 (Box 5, Folder 97)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (W. Stewart), 363055 (Box 5, Folder 98)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Valdez), 363054 (Box 5, Folder 99)
- L. 144 / Village (Willis), 363053 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Enrique Vega), 363052 (Box 5, Folder 101)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Whitfield I), 363051 (Box 5, Folder 102)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Whitfield II), 363050 (Box 5, Folder 103)
- Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Whitfield III), 363049 (Box 5, Folder 104)
- L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Woldeguiorguis), 363048 (Box 5, Folder 105)
- D.C. 37 / Board of Ed. (Ackrish), 363047 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- D.C. 37 / Bd. of Ed. (Bureau of School Supplies), 363046 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Aides Evander Childs and Forest Hills), 363045 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- D.C. 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Norah DeRespiris), 363044 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Doran and Stephens), 363043 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- D.C. 37 / Board of Ed (E. Gleich), 363042 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- D.C. 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Hannah Goldman), 363041 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Hamilton), 363040 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- D.C. 37 / Board of Ed (Harren High), 363039 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Hourly School Lunch Workers), 363038 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Julian), 363037 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Aide Sophie Kevelson; Walton High School), 363036 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Lucchini), 363035 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Aide JHS 189 Mrs. Esther Kriedman), 363034 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Maxwell), 363033 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Douglas Moore), 363032 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Mohamed Moussa), 363031 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Elizabeth Patterson), 363030 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Motor Vehicle Operators, BSL), 363029 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Wooten, et al), 363028 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Elizabeth Patterson), 363027 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (Scott), 363026 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (SPARK Program), 363025 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Aides Francis Lewis), 363024 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (James Purvis), 363023 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Neighborhood Workers 35 Hour Week), 363022 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- NABET/ABC AIO 80-1, 363021 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- NABET/ABC AIO 80-2, 363020 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- NABET/ABC AIO 83-1, 363019 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- NABET/ABC AIO 84-1, 363018 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- NABET/ABC AIO 84-2, 363017 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- NABET/ABC AIO 85-1, 363016 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- NABET/ABC ARW 77-5, 363015 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- NABET/ABC ARW 78-9, 363014 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- NABET/ABC ARW 78-10, 363013 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- NABET/ABC ARW 78-11, 363012 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- NABET/ABC ARW 78-14, 363011 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- NABET/ABC ARW 78-15, 363010 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- NABET/ABC ARW (Arbitrability 1979), 363009 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- NABET/ABC ARW 79-7, 363008 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- NABET/ABC ARW 79-9, 363007 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- NABET/ABC ARW 80-1, 363006 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- NABET/ABC ARW 80-5 & 6, 363005 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- NABET/ABC ARW 81-4, 363004 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- NABET/ABC ARW 81-8, 363003 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- NABET/ABC AWA 78-1, 363002 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- NABET/ABC AWA 79-2 / AWM 79-2, 363001 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- NABET/ABC AWA 79-3 / AWM 79-1, 363000 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- NABET/ABC AWA 80-3, 362999 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- NABET/ABC AW 75-33, 362998 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- NABET/ABC AW 76-6, 362997 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- NABET/ABC AW 76-17, 362996 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- NABET/ABC AW 76-203, 362995 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- NABET/ABC AW 77-11, 362994 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- NABET/ABC AW 77-32, 362993 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- NABET/ABC AW 77-35, 362992 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- NABET/ABC AW 77-36, 362991 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- NABET/ABC AW 78-1 (Ciraci and Perry), 362990 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- NABET/ABC AW 78-20, 362989 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- NABET/ABC AW 78-21, 362988 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- NABET/ABC AW 78-23 (TD Assignment), 362987 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- NABET/ABC AW 78-28, 362986 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- NABET/ABC AW 78-38 (Unilateral Audio by Non-NABETs), 362985 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-7, 362984 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-13, 362983 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-14, 362982 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-19 (Gruiff), 362981 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-22 (Microphone Clamps), 362980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-27, 362979 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-31, 362978 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-34, 362977 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-37, 362976 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-43, 362975 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-44, 362974 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- NABET/ABC AW 79-45, 362973 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- NABET/ABC AW 80-3, 362972 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- NABET/ABC AW 80-13, 362971 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- NABET/ABC AW 80-14, 362970 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- NABET/ABC AW 80-15, 362969 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- NABET/ABC AW 80-16, 362968 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- NABET/ABC AW 80-18, 362967 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- NABET/ABC AW 80-30, 362966 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- NABET/ABC AW 80-39, 362965 (Box 6, Folder 83)
- NABET/ABC AW 81-10 (20.10), 362964 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- NABET/ABC AW 81-27, 362963 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- NABET/ABC AW 81-64, 362962 (Box 6, Folder 86)
- NABET/ABC AW 81-42 (Hoover), 362961 (Box 6, Folder 87)
- NABET/ABC AW 81-45 (Champion), 362960 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- NABET/ABC AW 81-59 (20.10), 362959 (Box 6, Folder 89)
- NABET/ABC AW 81-61, 362958 (Box 6, Folder 90)
- NABET/ABC AW 81-63, 362957 (Box 6, Folder 91)
- NABET/ABC AW 82-6 (20.10), 362956 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- NABET/ABC AW 82-11, 362955 (Box 6, Folder 93)
- NABET/ABC AW 82-3, 362954 (Box 6, Folder 94)
- NABET/ABC AW 82-5, 362953 (Box 6, Folder 95)
- NABET/ABC AW 83-4, 362952 (Box 6, Folder 96)
- NABET/ABC AW 83-7, 362951 (Box 6, Folder 97)
- NABET/ABC AW 83-8, 362950 (Box 6, Folder 98)
- NABET/ABC AW 83-10, 362949 (Box 6, Folder 99)
- NABET/ABC AW 83-13, 362948 (Box 6, Folder 100)
- NABET/ABC AW 83-13 (20.10), 362947 (Box 6, Folder 101)
- NABET/ABC AW 83-19, 362946 (Box 6, Folder 102)
- NABET/ABC AW 84-8, 362945 (Box 6, Folder 103)
- NABET/ABC AW 84-12, 362944 (Box 6, Folder 104)
- NABET/ABC AW 84-9, 362943 (Box 6, Folder 105)
- NABET/ABC AW 85-10, 362942 (Box 6, Folder 106)
- NABET/ABC AW 85-11, 362941 (Box 6, Folder 107)
- NABET/ABC AW 85-24, 362940 (Box 6, Folder 108)
- NABET/ABC AW 86-1 (20.10), 362939 (Box 6, Folder 109)
- NABET/ABC AC 75-58, 362938 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- NABET/ABC AC 76-49, 362937 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- NABET/ABC AC 77-26, 362936 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- NABET/ABC AC 78-2, 362935 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- NABET/ABC AC 78-6, 362934 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- NABET/ABC AC 78-27, 362933 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- NABET/ABC AC 78-33, 362932 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- NABET/ABC AC 79-35, 362931 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- NABET/ABC AC 80-39, 362930 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- NABET/ABC AC 81-3 & 4, 362929 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- NABET/ABC AC 34 & 35, 362928 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- NABET/ABC AC 82-8 (Johnson), 362927 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- NABET/ABC AC 82-28, 362926 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- NABET/ABC AC 82-66, 362925 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- NABET/ABC AC 82-62, 362924 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- NABET/ABC AC 82-68, 362923 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- NABET/ABC AC 83-4 & 5, 362922 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- NABET/ABC AC 83-7, 362921 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- NABET/ABC AC 83-37 (20.10), 362920 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- NABET/ABC AC 83-87 (Hale), 362919 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- NABET/ABC AC 84-8, 362918 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- NABET/ABC AC 84-26, 362917 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- NABET/ABC AC 84-50, 52, 57, 59, 362916 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- NABET/ABC AC 84-86, 362915 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- NABET/ABC AC 84-90, 362914 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- NABET/ABC AC 84-104, 362913 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- NABET/ABC AC 84 (Baumgart), 362912 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- NABET/ABC AC 84-93, 362911 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- NABET/ABC AC 85-12, 362910 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- NABET/ABC AC 85-67, 362909 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- NABET/ABC AC 85-73 (Klingman), 362908 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- NABET/ABC AC 86-13 (Kolarik), 362907 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- NABET/ABC AC 86-25, 362906 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- NABET/ABC AH 84-120 (20.10), 362905 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- NABET/ABC AH 85-72 & 73, 362904 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Air Canada / Connectors, 362903 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Aero Mexico / IAM, 362902 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Air India / IBT, L. 732 (Staab), 362901 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Allied Pilots Association / Flagship Airlines (Al-Wardi), 362900 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Alaska Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants, 362899 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- AFA / Atlantic Coast Airlines (Robertson), 362898 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Alaska Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (737-900), 362897 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- American Airlines / APA (2000), 362896 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- American Eagle / ALPA (Interest Arbitration), 362895 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- American Eagle / AFA (Susan Daniels) AFA 22-52-1-111-02, 362894 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- American Eagle / AFA (Equipment Substitution) 22-99-02-34-99, 362893 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- American Eagle / AFA (22-99-02-02-01), 362892 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- American Eagle / ALPA (Vijzelman; 121-1102), 362891 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- American Eagle / ALPA (Training Freeze; MEC No. 2402), 362890 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- American Eagle / ALPA (Bulletin Board; MEC 1902 & 2202), 362889 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- American Eagle / AFA (Leon; AFA 22-49-01-02-04), 362888 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Continental Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (03-20; Bousquet), 362887 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Continental Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Holmberg 02-12), 362886 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Continental Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Ferry Flights 03-04), 362885 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Continental Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (Plummer; 02-03), 362884 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Continental Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (CRAF; 03-02), 362883 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Continental / Frontier, 362882 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Continental / International Association of Machinists (Flight Attendant), 362881 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Continental / IBT (Martinez Per Diem Pay), 362880 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Continental / IBT (0418 Group), 362879 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Continental / IBT (0456; Super Tug), 362878 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Eagle Electronic / Local 365, UAW (01567 90), 362877 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Delta / Air Line Pilots Association (ALT 02-39; Lake), 362876 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Express Jet / ALPA (Cocchiola), 362875 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Federal Express / Flying Tigers Award, 362874 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Federal Express / Flying Tigers (Dispute Resolution Committee), 362873 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Federal Express / Flying Tigers (Dispute Resolution Committee; Dilbeck), 362872 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Federal Express / Flying Tigers (The Broader Issue), 362871 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Federal Express / Flying Tigers (B747 Vacancies LAX), 362870 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Frontier / CWA (2316-03 & 2321-03; Temporary Employees), 362869 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Horizon / Association of Flight Attendants (06-17-2-08-01; Agency Stop), 362868 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Mesaba Aviation / Aircraft Mechanics Fraternal Association (Kingery), 362867 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Northwest / Air Line Pilots Association (Sutton), 362866 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- NWA / Pre-Merger Republic Pilots (92-111; monthly bidding), 362865 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- NWA / Pre-Merger Republic Pilots (92-104; Insufficient Bidders), 362864 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- NWA / International Association of Machinists (CSA Gate Screening), 362863 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- NWA / Air Line Pilots Association (2604-02; Hickman), 362862 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- NWA / IBT (02-223 & 02-226, force majeure), 362861 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- NWA / Republic of Airlines Pilot Merger Representatives (03-160; Replacement Aircraft), 362860 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- NWA / Republic of Airlines Pilot Merger Representatives (03-162), 362859 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (Denial of Awarded Patterns), 362858 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-158-84), 362857 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association and Flight Engineers International Association (Med./ Arb.), 362856 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-135-83), 362855 (Box 8, Folder 22)